Ah, hello, girlfriend.
あー、どうも彼女さん
Hello, it's been a while.
どうもどうも、お久しぶりです
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Girlfriend, are you okay today?
彼女さん、今日もいいですかね
We can have a little teasing and socializing like before.
前みたいに、からかの付き合い、ちょっとやっていただける
So that's it.
ということで
Come to think of it, for example, hasn't it happened before?
そう いえば、例えばね、前もっとあったじゃないですか
yes.
はい
After that, did something happen that you couldn't do?
その 後、無理で、何かあったりとかしてますか
Ah, hello, girlfriend.
あー、どうも彼女さん
Hello, it's been a while.
どう もどうも、お久しぶりです
Huh?
えっ
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Girlfriend, are you okay today?
彼女さん、今日もいいですかね
Um, like before.
あのー、前みたいに
Um, you can do a little bit of teasing and socializing.
あのー、からかの付き合い、ちょっとやっていただける
So that's it.
ということで
yes.
はい
Is that okay?
いい ですかね
yes.
はい
I see.
なるほど
Okay, uh, let's go together from now on.
いいですか、あのー、一緒にこれから、
It's like being in animal mode at a hotel.
ちょっとホテルで動物モードみたいな
May I.
いいですか
yes.
はい
It's good to be in a good mood.
ノリノリいいですね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Understood.
分かりました
So, uh, that's right.
じゃあ、あのー、そうですね
The venue for the teasing party will be over here.
あの、からかの付き合いの会場、こっちになるんで
yes.
はい
Shall we go?
行きましょうか
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
First of all, there's a lot of things, like the hotel room,
最初にいろいろ、からかのシー、ホテルのね、
It's coming soon.
近くの到着ですね
yes.
はい
Hmm, ah, that seems like it.
うーん、あ、そうだそうだ
Um, now that I think about it, for example, uh...
あの、そういえば、例えばね、あのー、
It happened before, right?
前ことあったじゃないですか
Did you know that Puri originally existed?
プ リで、元々あったりとかって知ってますか?
I know.
知ってる
Oh my god.
あらあらあらあら
I see.
なるほど
For some reason, when I was in the entertainment industry, I was quite restrained about my private life.
なんか、芸能の時とかに、プライベートは結構我慢してたから
I see.
なるほど
I see, it's pretty realistic.
なるほど、結構リアルリアル
Yeah.
うん
I see.
なるほどね
Well, that's how it is sometimes.
まあ、それでね、たまにはって感じで
Sometimes?
たまには?
Yes, I look at men who are excited.
そう、なんか、興奮してる男の人とか眺めるの、
I really like it.
結構好きだなって
Seriously?
マ ジで?
Yeah.
うん
I see.
なるほど
It doesn't look like that, but it's actually a little exciting.
そんな風に見えないですけども、実はそれがちょっと興奮すると
I just wanted to accept it all.
とか、なんか、すべて受け入りたくて
Oh my god.
あらあらあ
I see.
なるほど
Well, since April, yeah yeah.
まあ、4月から、 うん うん
Since it goes so far, I don't think I need to know everything about the body.
余計進むから、体のことも全部知っとかないとかな
I see.
なるほど
Well then, let's have a little old man's body,
じゃあ、ちょっとおじさんの体でね、
Well, let me tell you a little bit about the body.
ちょっとあの、ね、ちょっと体のこと教えますので
OK, I understand.
OK、分かりました
Well, let's go.
じゃあ、行きましょうか
What, can I feel your nipples?
なに、乳首感じるの?
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Yeah.
うん